Let's talk about managing your staff
lists.
Everything we're going to do
is going to be from the staff list page.
So the first thing we're going to do
is add
somebody to our staff list.
Our staff list here
is made up of departments.
So let's say we want to add somebody
to the administration department.
We click on our context
menu here a little pencil.
If you're having trouble with,
you know hovering over all of these to,
to get them to show up and you're
not quite sure what you can edit
if you go up here to the top
and you click edit,
that will turn all of them on.
So let's go to administration,
say edit department
and down here is our staff members.
And we can remove these.
We can edit these or we can add people.
We can either add an
existing person
or we can add a new person.
We can search for people here.
So let's say we wanted to add
Aaron to this department.
We would just select her.
We can drag people around
to change the order.
We can also add new people.
And have a biography that's not going to
show up on this page or the photo.
It will show up on other pages.
If we had, you know, like the,
the principals and things on there.
So let's click save.
And now here I am again.
We could rearrange.
We could also this is where if we have,
you know, department photos,
we can add them here.
So it's insert Media
where you have a picture I uploaded here.
And there it is.
Click save.
And now we have all of our new people
added to the administration.
Now it's remove
me from this department.
Go back to edit department.
Remove.
And I'm gone.
Let's say we wanted to edit somebody.
Let's say,
there's a typo in one of these,
people.
Instead of
clicking up here to edit the department.
We can come down
and edit the person.
And let's say there was a typo in
in this email address.
Okay.
Save it.
Come back and see that it's in fact fixed.
Now let's say we wanted to add
a whole new department to this page.
We want to edit the whole page.
So we'll click up here on Edit.
And here
we can see our whole list of departments.
So we
scroll all the way down to the bottom.
And you can see on this page
this is what's called an advanced page.
That means we can add different
content types to it.
And so what we're going to add
is a department.
So and then here
we can select our department.
We could
use an existing department.
We could create a new department.
And our description.
Add people just like we did before.
Here we're going to search for.
Click save.
And now we have our department here.
We can rearrange these if I want to drag
my new department up.
Now you can see since these departments
are they're kind of big.
So it's kind of hard to drag these around.
So there's a feature up here.
At the top.
We can look at all of our content blocks.
And we can say we want to do a drag
and drop overview.
This will tell us
here's our Department of Fun.
I'm going to bring this all the way up.
Right under administration.
And we want to make sure that we click
here on complete drag and drop.
Scroll down to the bottom.
Click save.
Now we can see
our new department is there.